fresh2refresh.com 2017-09-15

# Privacy Policy | fresh2refresh.com

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed our Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

> 1\. Online Compilers - Compile & Run your C/C++ programs: 
> 
> ##### [✅ Online Compilers](http://compilers.fresh2refresh.com/)
> 
> 2\. Ask your questions or clarify your/others doubts from, 
> 
> ##### [✅ Online Discussion Forums by Fresh2Refresh.com](http://fresh2refresh.com/discussion-forums/)

* * *

* * *

Close

We Support JALLIKATTU !!!

We Support JALLIKATTU!   
By Fresh2Refresh.com   
Show Your Support as well. Thanks!
